Next, add a copy of the D-circle to the back of the model.
Open the copy of Connect, select the hardware, and select Rings.
Find the D-circle.
Double-click to add to the object window.
Drag the D-circle from the object window to the 3D window.
In the open copy window, you can choose the location of the D-circle,
the original location or the location of the coordinate 0, 0.
Here, select the original location and the location when the D-circle is stored.
Use the move tool to select the D-circle.
There are three tools in the upper right corner.
Next, we will apply these three tools.
First, single-click to start the first quick arrangement tool.
When the mouse moves on the costume,
you can see the gray shadow of the D-circle moving with the mouse,
and it is in the position where the D-circle moves.
When you come to the location near the target,
you can easily and quickly place the D-circle near the target location.
Again, single-click to start the third glue tool.
In the appropriate position,
single-click to move the D-circle to this position.
You can use the positioning ball to slightly move the D-circle.
In the object window, select the D-circle component,
and in the property editor,
select its specification property.
First, you can enter the name of the component,
product number, and other information.
The proportion in the specification can be adjusted
to the size of the component in the X, Y, and Z axis.
The default fixed proportion is used.
You can adjust the size according to the proportion.
In the weight column, set the weight of the component.
The input weight value will be reflected in the simulation.
Under the material, you can set the material type of the component.
In addition, there is another way to adjust the size of the component.
After selecting the component with the move tool,
single-click on this square icon.
The coordinates are changed to the shrink adjustment coordinates.
The mouse is placed on the red, green, blue coordinate axis separately.
When the left key is pressed and the mouse is moved,
the size of the corresponding direction of the component can be changed.
If you want to increase or decrease the proportion,
put the mouse on the left mouse button.
In this way,
the mouse is placed on the gray, three-dimensional square in the middle.
The mouse is changed to a diagonal arrowhead.
The left key is pressed and moved,
and the proportion can be reduced according to the size of the component.
After adjusting the size,
single-click on the icon to close this coordinate.
The terrain ring is in the selected state.
The property editor can edit its conflict thickness and rigidity.
The component simulation is carried out below.
The component simulation can carry out the movement of the B pin,
and interact stably with the 3D clothing.
Before simulation,
right-click on the component first,
to ensure that the activation is activated.
Then,
click to simulate.
You can see the terrain ring collides and simulate between the panels naturally.
After stabilization,
close the simulation.
The terrain ring is added and completed.
Right-click on the terrain ring again.
The simulation column is removed from the activation.
There are two other options.
Freeze and Reactivate.
For the component,
if you only want it to collide with the panel,
and not move,
select Freeze.
If you want to stop the collision and simulate at the same time,
select Reactivate.
Finally, the completed component will be saved.
Select it in the object window.
In the property editor,
click Save.
Save the component in the .trm file format,
so that it can be used later.
Now,
model a state of the area .
Select this state.
Go back to the model .
Select the .trm function.
Select the .trm object from the .trm tutorial.
Select .
Select .trm .
Click .